NYS PERB Harold Newman Files 6173
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
NYS PERB Harold Newman Files
1965-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State Public Employee Relations Board (NYS PERB)
Newman, Harold
6173
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
5830494
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 09, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 24, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5140: NYS PERB Agreements 6257: NYS PERB "The Taylor Law On Its 40th Anniversary" Publication
Arrangement
Series I. Harold Newman Speeches, 1978-1990
Series II. Correspondence and Subject Files., 1965-2000
Series III. Publications, 1966-2002
Series IV. Harold Newman Scrapbook.
Employee-management relations in government -- Law and legislation -- New York (State); Labor disputes -- New York (State); Civil service -- New York (State); Collective bargaining -- Government employees -- New York (State); Newman, Harold; New York (State). Public Employment Relations Board
5830494
- Series I. Harold Newman Speeches, 1978-1990
  - 1978 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1978 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1985 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1985 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1986 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1986 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1990 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 1990 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Series II. Correspondence and Subject Files., 1965-2000
  - 3/1/1965 - 10/10/1979, 1965-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 3/1/1980 - 12/16/1983, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1/11/1984 - 11/12/1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1/30/1985 - 12/10/1985, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 1/2/1986 - 12/9/1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1/13/1987 - 12/17/1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 2/10/1988 - 11/1/1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1/17/1989 - 11/1/1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1/3/1990 - 12/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - 1/5/1991 - 12/23/1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 5/6/1992 - 8/7/1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 2/2/1993 - 12/14/1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 1/24/1994 - 2/2/1995, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 9/9/1996 - 3/18/2000, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous and undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Series III. Publications, 1966-2002
  - "How to be a Super Conciliator" (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Industrial Relations Review, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Labor History Month Article for PERB News (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Labor Law Journal, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Scope and Contents
    October, 1986.
  - "Labor Relations in the '90s - How did we get here and where shall we go from here" (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - "Mediation and Fact-Finding" (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - PERB News, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    1994-1995 Annual Report Edition
  - PERB News, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    1995-1996 Annual Report Edition
  - PERB News, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    12/1986 - 12/1989
  - PERB News, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    4/1990 - 12/1992
  - PERB News, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    1/1993 - 12/1994
  - PERB News, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    5/1996 - 12/2002
  - Perspective Article (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Public Relations Journal, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    May, 1966.
  - The Review, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Summer 1980
  - "The State Report" (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - "The Taylor Law" (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - "The Transport Workers Union of America - the Irish Connection," Cronin, Sean (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Series IV. Harold Newman Scrapbook.
  - Scrapbook (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Contains private correspondence, photographs, and newspaper clippings.